[
  {"question": "ر ا ل د و ن و", "answer": "رونالدو"},
  {"question": "س ي م ي", "answer": "ميسي"},
  {"question": "ب ر ش ل و ن ة", "answer": "برشلونة"},
  {"question": "م د ر ي د", "answer": "مدريد"},
  {"question": "ن ي و ي و ر ك", "answer": "نيويورك"},
  {"question": "ل ن د ن", "answer": "لندن"},
  {"question": "ب ا ر ي س", "answer": "باريس"},
  {"question": "ت و ك ي و", "answer": "طوكيو"},
  {"question": "ك ا ن د ا", "answer": "كاندا"},
  {"question": "ب ي ج و", "answer": "بيجو"}
]
